[
  {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "Which exercise primarily targets the chest muscles?",
    "options": [" Deadlift", "Bicep Curl", "Bench Press", "Leg Press"],
    "answer": "Bench Press"
  },
  {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "What does BMI stand for??",
    "options": [
      "Basic Muscle Index",
      "Body Mass Index",
      "Balanced Metabolic Indicator",
      "Body Maintenance Index"
    ],
    "answer": "+Body Mass Index"
  },
  {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of stretching before a workout?",
    "options": [
      " Build Muscle",
      "Increase Heart Rate",
      "Improve Flexibility",
      "Burn Calories"
    ],
    "answer": "Improve Flexibility"
  },
  {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "Which nutrient is commonly referred to as the body's building blocks?",
    "options": ["Carbohydrates", "Protein", "Fat", "Vitamins"],
    "answer": "Protein"
  },
  {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "What does DOMS stand for in the context of fitness?",
    "options": [
      "Daily Overall Muscle Strain",
      "Delayed Onset Muscle Soreness",
      "Dynamic Oxygen Movement System",
      "Daily Oxygenation Maintenance System"
    ],
    "answer": "Delayed Onset Muscle Soreness"
  },
  {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "What is the recommended daily water intake for an average adult engaging in regular physical activity?",
    "options": ["1 liter", "3 liter", "5 liter", "8 liter"],
    "answer": "8 liter"
  },
  {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "Which of the following is a compound exercise?",
    "options": [" Bicep Curl", " Leg Extension", "Squat", "Tricep Kickback"],
    "answer": "Squat"
  },
  {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "What is the purpose of a cooldown after a workout?",
    "options": [
      " Increase Heart Rate",
      "Burn Additional Calories",
      "Prevent Dizziness",
      "Promote Recovery and Flexibility"
    ],
    "answer": "Promote Recovery and Flexibility"
  },
  {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "How many days a week is it generally recommended to engage in aerobic exercise for overall health?",
    "options": ["1-2 days", "3-4 days", "5-6 days", "Every day"],
    "answer": "5-6 days"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "What is the term for the number of calories burned at rest to maintain basic physiological functions?",
    "options": [
      "Active Metabolic Rate",
      " Basal Metabolic Rate",
      "Exercise Metabolic Rate",
      "Maximum Metabolic Rate"
    ],
    "answer": " Basal Metabolic Rate"
  }
]
